[{'type': 'boolean', 'difficulty': 'medium', 'category': 'Science &amp; Nature', 'question': 'Polaris is the brightest star in the northern hemisphere night sky.', 'correct_answer': 'False', 'incorrect_answers': ['True']}, {'type': 'boolean', 'difficulty': 'hard', 'category': 'Vehicles', 'question': 'In 1993 Swedish car manufacturer Saab experimented with replacing the steering wheel with a joystick in a Saab 9000.', 'correct_answer': 'True', 'incorrect_answers': ['False']}, {'type': 'boolean', 'difficulty': 'easy', 'category': 'Entertainment: Video Games', 'question': 'In RuneScape, one must complete the &quot;Dragon Slayer&quot; quest before equipping Rune Platelegs.', 'correct_answer': 'False', 'incorrect_answers': ['True']}, {'type': 'boolean', 'difficulty': 'easy', 'category': 'Geography', 'question': 'San Marino is the only country completely surrounded by another country.', 'correct_answer': 'False', 'incorrect_answers': ['True']}, {'type': 'boolean', 'difficulty': 'medium', 'category': 'Animals', 'question': 'An octopus can fit through any hole larger than its beak.', 'correct_answer': 'True', 'incorrect_answers': ['False']}, {'type': 'boolean', 'difficulty': 'easy', 'category': 'Entertainment: Video Games', 'question': 'Deus Ex (2000) does not feature the World Trade Center because it was destroyed by terrorist attacks according to the game&#039;s plot.', 'correct_answer': 'True', 'incorrect_answers': ['False']}, {'type': 'boolean', 'difficulty': 'medium', 'category': 'Animals', 'question': '&quot;Kamea,&quot; the Gilbertese Islander word for dog, is derived from the English phrase &quot;Come here!&quot;', 'correct_answer': 'True', 'incorrect_answers': ['False']}, {'type': 'boolean', 'difficulty': 'medium', 'category': 'Animals', 'question': 'Sea sponges can have hearts.', 'correct_answer': 'False', 'incorrect_answers': ['True']}, {'type': 'boolean', 'difficulty': 'easy', 'category': 'Entertainment: Video Games', 'question': 'Rollercoaster Tycoon 1 and 2 were developed by Chris Sawyer.', 'correct_answer': 'True', 'incorrect_answers': ['False']}, {'type': 'boolean', 'difficulty': 'medium', 'category': 'History', 'question': '&quot;I disapprove of what you say, but I will defend to the death your right to say it&quot; is a quote from French philosopher Voltaire.', 'correct_answer': 'False', 'incorrect_answers': ['True']}]